genetic profile.
Confirmed entry authorised.
Greetings, Doctor.
So
step inside
355,500 days for your meeting with Mr
Please proceed to the 35th.
Wait 350,000.
That's hundreds of years ago.
What's going on?
Forget about travelling light.
The protocols used Polly physic and tangled way forms.
Quantum encryption, black court stuff, way beyond military grade.
That's what you demand it.
So that's what we delivered.
You don't code something you can't crap.
All we need is a backdoor love.
The latest service.
Pack up data and the problem goes away.
You specifically forbade us from leaving anything resembling a backdoor code.
Every protocol, the black court's standard your words.
Look, if you need me to fudge some projections, it's nothing we haven't done before.
I don't need fucking projections.
I need a way to reassert control over the heart's team or swear I don't know what to tell you.
Dead,
you're asking the impossible.
So codes They needed codes of some kind to control the machines, but they got out of control.
Sounds bad.
You
I can't spare the weight.
Just bring her
a statue.
A machine built to kill they honoured it.
Welcome to Farrell Automated Solutions, where all the problems of tomorrow are being solved.
Today, with over 25,000 human employees based in nations and corporate holdings across the globe, Farrell leads the world in every sector of self sustaining, fully automated technology, from revolutionary consumer products close to home.
Like the focus to the dynamic chariot line of peace keeping robots halting bloodshed in conflict zones across the globe, Farrell remains committed to making the future smarter, brighter, safer and always surprising.
Farrell.
Automated solutions for every problem of life.
A smart solution.
So they made the focus.
25,000 people.
That's bigger than a trial.
So they made machines and devices.
I guess things for common in their world.
Yeah,
what was this place?
But what were they doing here?
It was a corporation.
A group of people not unlike a tribe
made machines.
Yeah, go on.
I have a bloated some data files to focus.
They will help you understand
Association of individuals created under authority of law, having existence powers and liabilities distinct from those of its members.
In a business sense, a corporation is usually owned by shareholders through the sale or distribution of stock who profit from such ownership.
Voted designated times for its governance and designate executives who run its affairs.
Most corporations engage in one or more industries to produce goods or offer services for profit and may in turn known other corporations, companies or properties.
Holdings
Reception Lug.
July 7th 2064 9:54 a.m. Field Common denting of the Indo Millie agricultural combine arrived with his delegation Refreshments to be served before their 10:15 a.m. sales presentation on the chariot line for instructions.
Food will be vegetarian only 10:07 a.m. Sander Agnew, vice president of territorial Integrity from Fresh Grounds Coffee Global, arrived with his entourage.
Refreshments to be served before their 10:30 a.m. sales presentation on the chariot line.
For instructions.
Will use fresh grounds to coma blend.
No artificial creamers.
10:12 a.m.
so that happened.
I called security and janitorial to clean up the coffee that was spilled, actually more like thrown.
I wasn't aware that the Indo Malay combine grows coffee beans and that Fresh Grounds acquisition team has tried to take their fields by force repeatedly.
I think common damn thing had Agnew by the hair for a second there who schedules thes things.
I'm going to drop a line to sales.
This can't happen again.
Zero Automated Solutions Fast is an American multinational corporate entity that produces robots for all walks of life, though its core business consists of military and defence contracts.
As of 2063 Fast has ranked number one among the Fortune five by gross revenue and profit for 10 years in a row.
A world record founded in 2033 by Teodor Ted Pharaoh, an entrepreneur from Salt Lake City, Utah, the company developed several promising robot prototypes in its early years but failed to break into markets dominated by then industry giants like General Synthetics and Record.
This changed in 2038 with a debut with the Alfred Line of levitating personal Sir Vitter's, which generated exceptional sales, lifting the company into the Fortune 50 for the first time.
Profits tripled in the 2040 says the company's environmental efforts, led by famed engineer Elizabeth Sobek, catapulted fast to the head of that sector in 2049 in the wake of the successful green and climate cleanup efforts around the globe.
Worldwide approval ratings of Fat succeeded 90% and founder Ted Pharaoh was hailed across media and social networks as the man who saved the world.
Yet it was the emergence of Fast as a military contractor in the late 20 forty's that cemented its status as the world's wealthiest corporation, with a record market capitalisation of over $23 trillion by 2055 has controlled 61% of the market share for automated military platforms, holding contracts with 353 nations, trans governmental organisations and corporate entities.
Today it's holding Succeed the second largest corporation.
FB Moby.
How Global, by 321%
Pharaoh, born December 24th 2013, is an American entrepreneur and business magnate.
He is the founder of Pharaoh Automated Solutions, Fast the largest corporation of all time, the world's wealthiest individual and the first ever trillionaire.
Born and raised in Salt Lake City, Utah, he enrolled at the University of California, Los Angeles, where he studied business for two years before dropping out in 2033 to start.
Fans struggled at first.
The company broke through at the end of the troubled 20 thirties with its popular lines of personal surveyors and body guard bots, then exploded when its famous line of green robots led the race to solve the climate crisis during the 20 forty's.
Claw back at the end of that decade has opened a military defence branch dominating the world market for automated military platforms.
By 2053.
The success of fans has made Mr Farrow the world's best known businessmen, one of its most sought after speakers and a major voice in politics, culture and international affairs.
Elizabeth, born March 11th 2020 is an American scientist, roboticist and engineer widely regarded as one of the greatest minds of the 21st century.
Born and raised outside Carson City, Nevada, she enrolled at Stanford University at age 13, earning a B S and experimental physics and computer science.
At age 16, she completed her PhD in robotics and artificial intelligence, designed at Carnegie Mellon University in 2040 and Joint Pharaoh Automated Solutions as a junior scientist the same year, rising quickly to chief scientist at the age of 22.
Over the next eight years, her green robot designs played a vital role in realising the environmental cleanup in detoxification efforts of the claw back decades propelling fest to the forefront of its field.
In 2048 she suddenly resigned from fans protesting the company's pivot to automated military technologies.
In 2049 she founded Miriam Technologies, a firm devoted to life, positive robotics and other technologies.
Miriam has since become one of the world's largest suppliers of green robots, winning numerous awards and accolades, including the 2053 Nobel Prize for Physics in the 2056 Rachel Carson Award for Environmental Progress.
Yeah,
yeah,
now I know this must seem like a bizarre, changing direction.
I mean, with Sarah Automatic Solutions, right, Number one robotics firm in the world.
Why would we clear our production slate to fabricate human operated vehicles and weapons systems?
The relics of the past?
All I can say at this juncture is
trust me.
We will be exploiting a message
growth opportunity by retooling and reallocating capacity according to my plan.
So I will need revised projections of mass fabrication velocity across every pipeline within 36 hours.
So they were making machines when they start to make other kinds of weapons.
Boy,
see there.
There's no smell to it.
Not even old death.
Nothing natural.
Should have brought a cart.
Another cave in.
But I could get through
from J freakin to reception.
Subject.
Re complaint.
Hey, reception.
If that is your real name, Wanna know who's scheduled?
Indo Malay, right next to fresh grounds.
That would be me senior v p of sales.
I want to know why.
After that little hair pulling incident, both sides increased their bids by 40%.
I'll explain because your receptionist level brain probably requires it.
Those two sides are fighting.
And what do we sell?
That's right.
Combat machines.
We want them to hate each other so they will try to fight each other.
With what?
That's right again.
Combat machines, which they will pay us a lot of money for.
So I suggest you go back to serving coffee with a blank smile and let me do my much more complicated job.
Thanks a bunch, Mr Friedkin to you.
No,
Looks like I can climb here,
but I can use that as a ramp to get back up.
You?
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
The F s P five cowfish provides a one size fits all solution to main battle force capability.
Medic Material Construction delivers unmatched record dampening, allowing you to feel any weapon package that conforms to your budget needs and conflict resolution Profile.
Patented biomass conversion systems allow extended emergency operations with minimal environmental impact.
Multi linear target processing provides simultaneous real time threat analysis and legal review for autonomous domestic operations or control.
Could be slave to the swarms Neural network for weapons free force application.
Either way, when it's time to call out the big guns, it's time to call cowfish death bringer.
So this was the heavy hitter Main battle force Indeed.
The B o.
R.
Seven.
Horace Imagine your complete engagement ecosystem comprehensively managed by high speed Learning Machine Network.
Whether your need is to replace battlefield losses or intensify force projection, the Horace is onboard.
Manufacturing capabilities mean you'll never get stuck waiting for the next arms delivery.
Simply redefine your fourth parameters and the Horace will fabricate additional units to fill the ranks for a GN affordable per unit licencing feet.
Meanwhile, the biomass conversion systems of other chariot line models allow them to keep the Horace fuelled, repaired and ready.
Extending its operational tolerance is beyond that of any competing tightening class platform.
That's the Horace advantage.
Always regulating, always ready.
The future of automated warfare made real today.
Metal devil.
So these were far machines, too.
Manufacturing capabilities.
They could make more of themselves.
How would you ever stop them?
The A three Scattered combines conventional and information warfare capabilities in one package designed for high speed, all terrain reconnaissance, it boasts the world's highest survivability rating of any scout class autonomous agent.
Maybe it's the scarabs emergency biomass conversion systems that ensure it always makes it back to base, even if you'll supply lines have been interdicted.
Or maybe it's the scarabs ability to slave enemy robots to its own network.
Now that's forced multiplication at a pretence I'll manipulator arm that can handle the host of functions from 360 degree less lethal riot management to surgical repairs of Allied chariot line marks.
And you've got the workhorse of any cutting edge peacekeeping fleet.
It's a corruptor slave enemy robots to its own network.
It sounds like it's talking about how corrupt machines
go
from Ted Pharaoh to Paul of Azzurra subject spirituals summit Paula Recent events have sharpened my perspective and I think that I and Fasten General have been neglecting the spiritual side of things.
Not under any specific religious framework, of course, but in a more general sense as enough giving enough thought to our shared values, hopes and aspirations for the afterlife.
I'd like you to reach out to religious leaders of every stripe with the intention of scheduling a conference soon.
Very soon, I'll have more thoughts about the agenda later.
But for now, let's put out some feelers and see if we can lock something in.
Make it a big tent.
No cooks, but anyone with a credible audience.
Let's go deluxe.
Make it clear we'll spare no expense.
Thanks, Ted.
I'd have to ditch something.
No
high priority Alert.
Automated lock.
Note.
All non essential systems have entered hibernation.
High priority alert.
Automated lock note.
Full lock down has been initiated.
High priority alert.
Due to the increasing frequency of violent protests targeting the campus, the security of FAZ employees can no longer be guaranteed.
Therefore, we have taken the difficult decision to shutter this facility indefinitely.
Staff will be briefed on a block by block basis regarding proper procedure for archiving and or disposal of project related data and materials.
Hi Second a Crisis Team within Conduct Exit review before all areas air lock down high Priority alert Priority messaging to all staff in the n f blocks.
Treat.
The current lock down situation is an exercise, but do not attempt to release the hatches or otherwise exit the buildings.
High priority alert A reminder that while high SEC personnel remained committed to employee safety during the current unfortunate events, personal firearms must be relinquished when presenting for identity.
Scan high priority alert.
Additional public access roads en route to the campus have now been closed to relieve waiting time at the outer Security cordons.
Hi SEC Reminds all staff that the campus remains off limits to the public high priority alert Following recent campus security issues, all staff are reminded that presenting for identity scan and displaying your security badge prominently at all times for image analytics are both mandatory high priority alert in light of recent acts of terrorism directed at the rapid transit system.
Hi SEC now offers a Big Brother initiative to accompany staff travelling from off site.
Sign up is required and strongly encouraged.
48 more entries in high priority.
Additional entries corrupted.
So people were angry at Faro.
But the corporation
they blame this place for something.
Something bad.
Go.
Looks like the way up.
What's left of it.
Gonna be a long way up.
Frozen metal most of the way.
I'm not making this easy, Dr.
Servic.
Plants can find a way to hang on up here.
Yes, I can do
who?
Yeah,
no
freezing out here.
This is the began when they engaged in unauthorised offensive operations against robots and human personnel of the heart's team or energy combine.
Now I wish that I could relate that the crisis has been
exaggerated, but it's not.
The peacekeepers have not responded to stand down coats and bio signs.
They appear to be replicating at a
precipitous right now.
What I can't promise and absolutely sure you is that I am already developing every possible resource towards reaching speedy conclusion to this issue.
So when you hear the bad talk about us against this company in the days, maybe weeks to come, I'm just very mind that we will get past.
It's that day's coming, but none of this will matter.
Peacekeepers.
That's what they called their machines.
They were built for war, not peace.
You
tasty.
Okay.
From Gordon Nakada to Gina's German subject.
All hands on deck, Gina.
Ever hear of the Melville Island Fruit Association?
Neither had I until they filed suit against us this morning.
Apparently, there's a little island paradise off the coast of Australia, population 2700 all of whom he does now that a stray hearts team where unit is chowing down on their largest mango orchard.
That brings the official count of Hearts team or related lawsuits to 127 most of them from private companies but also a bunch from individuals, nation states and NGOs.
And that's not even counting the mother of all liability claims from hearts itself.
Call every external firm we've ever used, then call their competitors.
We're going to need every corporate defence lawyer we confined who still have soba.
And on the bar.
Gordon Nakata, associate general counsel Fast.
I got too much already.
Yeah,
you.
It's
go.
Thank you.
From Stacy Anders to Robert Rusher.
Subject Dolphin did Bob another problem to add to our big steaming pile.
Apparently a fisherman in the bond ISI captured video of the heart's team or horse unit.
Refuelling vibe, bio matter conversion along the shoreline of Pulau Wetter on a pot of endangered dolphins, no less, quite possibly the last of their kind.
Not to get graphic, but it looks like what happens inside a blender, as if the robot was whipping up a big, pink, swirling milkshake of dolphin chum.
Our suppression team has scrapped it from 43 networks, but it's still propagating, so it's only a matter of time before it goes viral.
A prepared statement feels grossly insufficient.
Any suggestions?
This one's a real stinker.
Stays Sanders V P P.
R.
Fast
a way off.
All it takes is a few good handholds.
All right, I made it.
I'd have to ditch something.
No
power cells.
I'll need it to get to the armour in that ancient ruin, I found
I should have brought it, Kurt.
Okay.
And being raised by Mr Do You wish to deploy privileges to recover?
Yes, I believe I do.
Fans.
Elizabeth, get Teo.
It's been years.
Where's your legal team, Ted?
No need.
Dropped all 18 lawsuits.
Simoni landed.
I assume your daddy confirms us.
All right.
This promises to be interesting.
Perhaps we could have lunch brought in.
You okay?
You, Ted, You screwed something up to something bigger.
You wouldn't have eaten the crow necessary to get me here.
So spit it out.
There's
a glitch in the chariot line.
Your killer robots?
Peacekeepers?
Yes, those.
So should I do,
Officer?
I was.
We would if we coat.
They're not responding.
Are you telling me a swarm has gone rogue?
Ted,
it's worse than that.
Surely the data then
and we'll take that lunch alone.
Ted, far abroad was a bit so big here, but they hated each other.
I don't know.
No,
this isn't a glitch.
It's a catastrophe.
Fully aware.
It's bad.
Bad Jesus.
Less.
It's not bad, Ted.
It's apocalyptic.
You built a line of killer robots, peace keepers that consume biomass as fuel in emergencies.
And you made them capable of self application.
Limited self manufacture controlled.
Not anymore.
The glitch suffered chain of command.
The only nation that swarm answers to now is it stuff you could you think everything else is just food and at the rate it's replicating, Ted, it will strip the Earth bear in 15 months.
We're not talking.
Follow civilisation.
We're talking extinction.
I get it.
How?
Stop it while it's contained.
If not contained, it can't be.
You know what I mean?
Right before the truth gets out.
You mean was I will do anything you say.
Keep working it on.
Whatever you recommend.
I'll do.
I'm gonna hold you to that dead
far.
Robots threatened all life on Earth, but somehow she defeated them.
The world of the old ones fell, but life went on or we wouldn't be here.
Finally,
Project zero Dawn
Chase is less.
There has to be another way.
If there a nicer way to fix your mess.
I would have proposed it
thiss
when I asked you to find a cure.
I didn't expect it to be worse than the disease.
It's not Ted.
It may be grim, but it's our only chance.
Now sign the proposal.
I signed it.
I can't sign that.
Yes, you can.
That Liz, I cannot in good conscience sign that You've got a choice, Ted.
I know.
I'm speaking to you from a Vitale en route to us Robot Command.
In 15 minutes, I meet with General Harris and the rest of the Joint Chiefs.
What
you crazy.
Now your choice is what I tell them.
Sign and I'll tell them the wealthiest corporation on Earth has guaranteed the funds necessary to build zero Don,
exactly as I designed it or don't sign.
And I will make sure they and everyone else on this planet knows the real cause of the glitch.
Jesus less.
You don't have to threaten me
outside.
Look on the bright side, Ted.
From here on out, you get to do what?
You've always been good at footing the bill while others get their hands dirty.
God forgive me.
What made her solution so terrible?
What does she do to stop the robots?
Executive excess
experts?
It doesn't add up.
So it couldn't have been my mother.
She lived ages ago.
Hold this searching and I'm still no closer.
That's your reaction to everything.
You just learned the wind like a spoiled child.
He should really try talking that way to me.
Face to face.
As you wish.
Do you really have no idea how monumental our the discoveries you just made a lawyer?
I expected more of you.
So you have a face.
Got a name to go with it of all the questions you could ask.
Right now, that's the one you choose.
I've spent a decade searching the ruins of the old ones, trying to solve the mystery of what happened to them.
For years I've suspected that feral robots destroyed their civilisation.
But I could never confirm it.
And in minutes you uncover more Incan knowledge, and I have in a lifetime.
And what you want to know
is my name.
If you're so smart, what do you know so little after a lifetime scratching around in the dirt?
It's not my fault.
You're bad at what you do.
I came to these ruins looking for Elizabeth Sobek, not because of the things she did centuries ago, but because people are trying to kill me right now.
Today,
I've got bigger problems to deal with in your crap.
Congratulations.
You just graduated from quieting to throw in a temper tantrum.
I'm sure Elizabeth would be proud.
You have no idea what I've been through, how hard it's been my whole life.
I grew up not knowing who I am or where I came from.
And then come the eclipse, trying to kill me just because I look like this Elizabeth Sobek woman and they killed the man who raised you.
And your found in the mountain is a baby.
I already know this through your focus.
You've been getting a free ride on my focus, risking nothing while I risk everything.
All I have to do is take this thing off my head and you'll be blind, deaf and dumb.
So quit complaining and answer my questions very well.
Silence.
That's my name.
No.
Why don't you try asking another question?
Something less trivial every time I take a step forward, the answer slipped farther from my grasp.
You just don't understand.
It's not that I don't understand the lawyer.
It's that I don't care
if he answers, keeps slipping away.
Every step you take the new best start running to catch up.
Maybe then you realise just how big your problems really are.
Alright, Silence.
You've made your point.
I came to these ruins hoping to learn more about this Elizabeth Sobek and I have.
But I still don't understand my Connexion to her or why the eclipse is trying to kill me or who Haiti's is no answers.
Just one question after another.
Who are you silence.
And what are your intentions?
They really need to make this personally.
I'm a lone wanderer who left his tribe behind a long time ago.
An explorer of forbidden places, a suitor of lost knowledge.
Exactly as I said, Why do you know so much about the eclipse?
I happen to know a lot about a lot of things.
If what you're really asking is whether I work for the eclipse or anyone else, I don't.
I'm nothing if not independent.
You've been using my focus to spy on me.
How is that possible?
Every focus emits a signal, a voice that only other focuses.
Come here.
I know how to string those voices together, how to make them talk to each other, to communicate even over vast distances.
How do you learn to do that?
Years of study and experimentation
and principal.
It's not so different from how you override machines.
I override focuses, and you, Khun Spy through other eclipses focuses, too.
Usually,
all I'll say is that overriding the connexions is
complicated.
That thing that spoke to me outside that made that focus explode
that was Haiti's.
The eclipse described him as a buried shadow.
Some kind of devil it it didn't seem like a person or a machine,
more like a phantom with a terrible voice.
All that Sutin
is that he wants you bid because of my Connexion To Elizabeth, it has to be Haiti's is using the eclipse to resurrect federal.
But you said you've known for some time that Farrah War machines destroyed the civilisation of the old ones.
The evidence pointed that way, but until now, I never need the full scope of the danger.
If they could process organic matter into fuel like a Horace class could manufacture more robots
like a coal drawn on legs.
But the robots we've seen so far the corrupters and death bring hers.
They don't do those things.
Not yet, anyway.
So far, we haven't encountered any that are undamaged at full power.
Who knows what they're capable of?
But if Elizabeth found a way to stop them centuries ago in some of the ancient dead I've recovered,
they're inside so called super weapons being developed.
Maybe Haiti's is worried I'll do the same thing.
This is speculation.
Wasting time.
Is there any chance that Elizabeth Sobek could still be alive?
Somehow?
It's highly unlikely she couldn't have been my mother if she lived centuries ago.
Some of the ancient dead I've recovered includes mentions of life extension techniques, pharmaceuticals, mostly an ancient word from medicine.
But Sam was still trying to perfect ways of freezing and on freezing people, phrasing and un phrasing people cryogenics, they called it.
But there were problems with it.
Given Elizabeth's technological acumen,
I can't definitively rule out that she found a way to make yourself immortal.
The only way to find out is to keep going to keep making discoveries.
Thanks to you, we've only just now learned that feral robots once threatened to end life on Earth.
But it didn't happen.
The old one civilisation was destroyed.
But life life was saved, obviously.
So
what get Elizabeth do?
How did she stuck the robots before?
All was lost.
What was Project Zero?
Don, Exactly the question Elizabeth told Ted Faro she was headed for a place called US Robot Command.
To tell people about zero Don place still exists is a ruin
the us or I'm calling the Grey Ford Grave horde Cherry name.
You'll find it in the Eastern Mountains, buried under the tangled coils of a Middle Devil or a Bor.
Seven Horace references were learning to call them.
I'll contact you when you get there.
I can't wait.
Some day we'll meet in person and your manners better.
Well, getting down will be a lot faster than getting up here.
At least
US Robot command Next.
Secrets of zero Dawn
Yes to the dynamic Carry it line of peacekeeping robots halting bloodshed in conflict zones across the globe.
Farrell remains committed to making the future smarter, brighter, safer and always surprising.
Farrell.
Automated solutions for every problem of life, a smart solution.